# Rozen Raymond

# FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPER

# **CONTACTS**

0415 337 031

rozenr.raymond@gmail.com

in linkedin.com/rozen-raymond

github.com/rozenraymond

Malaysian (Working Holiday Visa)

# **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Backbone HTML PostgreSQL CSS Sinatra Ruby *iOuery* Ruby On Rails D3.js JavaScript Three.js Node.js **SASS** React AJAX Phaser GitHub Underscore

#### OTHER SKILLS

PROJECT MANAGEMENT
PHOTOSHOP
ILLUSTRATOR

## **EDUCATION**

**GENEARL ASSEMBLY, SYDNEY** 

2016 - 2017

WEB DEVELOPMENT IMMERSIVE

# UNIVERSITY TECHNOLOGY PETRONAS

2011 - 2016

**B.A IN PETROLEUM GEOSCIENCES** 

## PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a motivated and passionate full stack developer with a background in geosciences. My previous experience was in the digital space working for a start up agency specialising in ad networks and mobile advertising.

My curiosity and interest towards technology has been my motivation in making the move to development. I love that the endless possibilities of tech means that, when used positively, we can continue to improve our daily lives and being in such a fast paced industry means that I am able to learn and discover new things everyday, which keeps me challenged.

I'm looking forward to working with a great team of developers in which I can continue to learn and grow.

#### **EXPERIENCES**

WEB DEVELOPMENT IMMERSIVE (OCT 2016 - JAN 2017)
GENERAL ASSEMBLY

Learned numerous frameworks, such as React & Backbone Built four websites using Ruby On Rails and JavaScript Exposure to unit testing using Rspec and Minitest

AGENCY SALES EXECUTIVE (APR - SEP 2016)
IMAGINE MOBILE

Handle day-to-day communications with new and existing clients

Manage and monitor implementation of media campaigns across APAC regions (HK, SG, MY, AU)

Work collaboratively with sales team and ad operations to provide strategy to meet revenue goals

Coordinate and oversee creative development with creative and developers team

GEOSCIENCES INTERN (JAN- APR 2015) BAKER HUGHES SDN BHD

FIELD ENGINEER INTERN (SEP - DEC 2014) BAKER HUGHES SDN BHD

RESEARCH ASSISTANT (SEP 2013 - JAN 2014)
SOUTHEAST ASIA RESEARCH LABORATORY

REFERES AVAILABLE UPON REQUEST